wiggio.com 2014-05-16

# Wiggio Privacy Policy

This policy is effective as of July 26, 2013.

Wiggio groups are private spaces and we are committed to maintaining the privacy of each individual group. There is no public directory of Wiggio groups. In order to maintain the privacy of each group, the ways to join a group are as follows:  

  * By invitation to a group via email or Facebook from a current member of the group who has the ability to invite other people;
  * By log-in to a group through use of a group name and password which only members of the group know; or
  * Through a link to enter the group, which they have been sent out by a group member with permissions to send out the link.

We are committed to providing the utmost in privacy and security. We do not sell or trade any personal information obtained from you through the Wiggio site.

Wiggio does not collect information from anyone without his/her consent. All e-mail correspondence is kept in strict privacy and will not be disclosed to third parties other than our affiliates or service providers, each of whom offers substantially similar privacy protections to those set out in this Privacy Policy.

By using Wiggio, you accept the practices described in this policy and acknowledge that our policies are subject to change at any time without notice.

## The Information We Collect 

When you visit Wiggio.com, you provide us with two types of information: (i) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose to us; and (ii) Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register with Wiggio, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, the school you attend and any other personal or preference information that you choose to provide to us.

When you enter Wiggio, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Wiggio visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a small piece of data placed on your web browser by an offering you use or a site you visit. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to the site. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

After you join Wiggio, you may set up groups and start using the Wiggio functionalities. You post your own content ("User Content") on the Site at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Wiggio is a violation of the Wiggio Terms of Use.

Wiggio may also collect information about you from other sources you use or that are connected to you, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of the Wiggio service through the operation of the service in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.

Information collected, posted or shared on Wiggio while logging on to the Site through Facebook Connect or using the Wiggio Application called "Wiggio Boards" on Facebook.com is being collected by Wiggio.

By using Wiggio, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and any other country in which Wiggio has affiliates or conducts business.

## Children Under the Age of 13 

By accessing, registering or using the Web Site, you represent to us that you (i) are at least the age of majority in your jurisdiction; OR (ii) you are at least 13 years old but under the age of majority in your jurisdiction AND you have consent from a parent or legal guardian to do so, and your parent or legal guardian has read and agreed to these Terms of Use. If you are under the age of 13, you may not use the Site unless we obtain consent from your parent or guardian in accordance with the procedure and form located here.

## Use of Information Obtained by Wiggio

When you register with Wiggio, you create and join groups and set your personal preferences. Your information and the content you generate is displayed to people in the groups you belong to on Wiggio. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by Wiggio that we think you may find valuable.

Wiggio may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message or poke, or someone posts on your wall, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.

Wiggio may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as determining how many people are in certain groups for advertisements and promotions.

## Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

Wiggio is about sharing information with the members of your groups. We reserve the right to do the following:

  * We may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the service at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about Wiggio, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, to offer an online job application process, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the Wiggio-specified purposes.

  * We occasionally provide demonstration accounts that allow non-users a glimpse into the Wiggio world. Such accounts have only limited capabilities (e.g., messaging is disabled) and passwords are changed regularly to limit possible misuse.

  * We may be required to disclose user information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the Wiggio service or using the Wiggio name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies.

  * We may offer services jointly with other companies on Wiggio. You can tell when another company is involved in any store or service provided on Wiggio, and we may share customer information with that company in connection with your use of that store or service.

  * If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Wiggio business were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time.

## Accessing and Correcting Your Personal Information

We offer users the ability to access or correct information we collect during registration or which they have provided in using Wiggio. Users may correct this information at any time and as often as necessary by using the features provided within Wiggio. To access or correct personal information collected by us that is not available through Wiggio, please contact us at the address listed below. We will respond within a reasonable timeframe of receiving your request or as otherwise required by law.

We may charge a fee for providing access to or correcting your information. If a fee may apply, we will inform you of the cost and request further direction from you on whether or not we should proceed with the request.

We may decline to provide you with access to, or to change, your personal information if (a) your request is not provided in writing, (b) your request does not provide us with sufficient detail to identify the personal information you seek to access or change, (c) we are unable to verify your identity to our satisfaction or (d) we deem, in our sole discretion, that it would be unreasonable in the circumstances to provide you with access to or to correct your personal information.

## User Opt-Out Option and Retention of Your Information

You may opt out of receiving promotional information from us by following the unsubscribe procedures indicated in any promotional information you receive.

We will retain your information for so long as you maintain an active account or user profile, or as needed to provide you with the applicable product or service offering.

If you wish to close an account you have with us, you may do so by contacting us at [feedback@wiggio.com](mailto:feedback@wiggio.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce this Privacy Policy and any applicable user agreements. We will take steps to ensure that your personal information is destroyed, erased or made anonymous as soon as the purpose for which it was collected is no longer relevant, or as required by law.

Please be aware that, as long as you have access to Wiggio, you cannot opt out of receiving service messages from us. Also, if we send communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with your receipt of messages on your mobile device (including text messaging charges).

## Information Accuracy, Currency and Reliability

We will maintain accurate, complete and up to date information based on the information submitted to us by our users. We rely on our users to inform us of changes to their personal information and, as such, are not responsible for the accuracy, currency or reliability of user-provided information obtained by us through Wiggio.

## Links

Wiggio may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Wiggio.com site and to information collected through it.

## Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on Wiggio are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Wiggio unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by us and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

## Security

We take appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors and agents who have a need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination, as well as civil action and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

We do not guarantee that we will eliminate all risk of misuse of your personal information. There is no such thing as perfect security, and we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any data (including personal information) that we receive and store on our or our service providers' systems. You are responsible for keeping any passwords secret to prevent unauthorized access to and use of any offerings to which you have access.

## European Union Data Protection

To the extent that we store data in the United States, we comply with the U.S.- European Union ("EU") Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from EU member countries.

If you reside in the European Union, upon registration for Wiggio you consent that the personal information you have provided may be transferred and stored in countries outside the EU.

## Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions

Your use of Wiggio, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. If we make changes, we will include them in this Privacy Policy and will indicate at the top of this page the Privacy Policy.s new effective date. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

## How to Contact Us

We commit to the resolution of complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.

Our Privacy Officer is responsible for ensuring our compliance with this Privacy Statement and all relevant privacy laws.

If you have any comments, questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement, the data that we collect from you or how that data is being used, or to report suspected misuse of your information, please contact us at privacy@desire2learn.com or write to us at:

Desire2Learn Incorporated   
Attn: Privacy Officer   
151 Charles Street West, Suite 400   
Kitchener, Ontario   
N2G 1H6 Canada   
cc: Legal Department

The Wiggio brand is owned by and is a trademark of Desire2Learn Incorporated.
